♪♪
-Let's get in the headspace here.
-Okay, just connect, yeah.
-I'm serious about this, right? You feeling it?
-Yeah, I'm feeling it. -Okay, yeah. Ready?
-Yeah.
-Fruits. -Okay.
-Three, two, one.
-Watermelon. -Apple.
[ Laughter ]
-Close. -Three, two, one.
-Guava. -Orange
-Guava? -[ Groans ]
I don't know why I said that.
Who the hell would guess guava? -Okay, okay.
We're trying to get the same thing.
-The same one, the same one. -Guava.
-I forgot you're from Australia. Is that a thing?
-I like guava. -Three, two, one.
-Banana -Kiwi.
You're from Australia.
Kiwi, isn't that a thing?
It's not from Australia.
That's Kiwi, New Zealand.
I mean, close, yes, yes.
My fault, my fault, my fault.
-Alright, let's go the next question.
Fruits, it didn't work. We didn't get an jinxes.
-Guava, why? -Guava?
-Yeah.
-Gosh.
[ Gasps ] Musical instruments.
-Okay. -Three, two, one.
-Guitar. -Guitar.
[ Ding ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Alright, we got a jinx on that one.
-I didn't even get the word out.
I was like guita... -Guita!
That was exciting. Alright, ready?
Body parts. Three, two, one.
-Stomach. -Ears
-Stomach?
[ Laughter ]
-I don't know. -I don't know, I guess.
-Okay, okay. -Three, two, one.
-Feet. -Lips.
[ Laughter ]
-Three, two, one.
-Elbow. -Nose.
-Alright, elbow.
Yeah, we didn't get that one.
Shapes. Three, two, one.
-Hexagon. -Rectangle.
No, I'm going to do -simple ones.
-Hexagon, sorry. I should have said hexagon.
-Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
-The first shape -- the first shape that
came to mind wasn't hexagon.
-They're obscure. I don't know why.
Okay, okay, okay. -Gosh.
I barely got through college.
Shapes. [ Laughter ]
Three, two, one
-Square. -Circle.
-Circle only has one.
Three, two, one.
-Triangle. -Triangle.
Yeah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Okay.
Alright, we have two jinxes
[ Whiffle! Boing! ]
I'm spewing.
-Margot, you keep spitting on me.
[ Whiffle! Boing! ]
Alright, stop with the sound effects.
-Hey, I'm not yelling "llama shoe" at you this time.
-I know. You were yelling at me, yeah.
-We're doing much better. -We're doing a speed round,
which means it's the same thing, We're just doing it faster.
-Oh, good.
'Cause because we were doing so well before anyway.
-Ready? Here you go. -Mm-hmm.
-Pies. Three, two, one.
-Meat pie. -Apple.
-Meat pie? -What?
[ Laughter and applause ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Meat pie.
[ Laughs ] Oh, my gosh.
-It's an Australian thing.
-[ Laughs ] -It's an Australian thing.
-It's an Australian thing. Sorry, sorry.
-Okay, American ones. Okay, okay.
-Types of balls. Three, two, one.
-Basket...ball. -Basketball.
[ Ding! ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Laughter ]
I'm legit crying.
-[ Laughs ]
All that went through my head was sweaty,
sweaty balls, sweaty balls.
[ Laughter ]
So, we both -- we both stopped ourselves.
-And I was like, "Don't say that on live television."
-Me too.
-Go for basketball.
-Alright, last one. Ready? Okay, okay, okay.
[ Chuckles ] God.
Oh, gosh.
Animals that you can --
Oh, sorry, it's animals that can eat you.
-T--
-Tiger -Tihyena.
-Sorry. Tihyena? -Tihyena
-Alright. Three, two, one.
-Lion. -Bear.
[ Buzzer ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Ready? -Okay, okay.
Reese Witherspoon.
-Reese Witherspoon?
[ Ding! ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
-You look at this! -I didn't look at it.
I love Reese Witherspoon. That's fantastic.
-Next time I'm going to go [mouths words].
-[ Laughs ] Don't do that. I didn't know what you're doing.
Alright, ready? Here you go.
-Oh.
-Yeah, that's good.
Huh?
[ Light laughter ]
[ Laughter ]
Bondi Beach.
-Um, one more.
-Bondi Beach.
[ Laughter ]
-A buzzing beach?
A bug beach.
-Bondi Beach. -Banana Beach.
-Bondi Beach. -Bada Beach
-Bondi Beach. -Bada-bada.
-Bondi Beach. -I'm get worse, I know.
[ Laughter ]
You're speaking Italian now.
Sorry, sorry, Here we go.
Bondi Beach.
-Bala...
[ Laughter ]
This is so hard.
-Alright. Bondi.
-Bonshi.
Bosh...
[ Laughter ]
I know I'm not saying anything in English.
-Bondi Beach.
-Posh and a beach.
[ Laughter ]
-Posh and a beach. No.
Bondi Beach. -Bondi Beach.
-Oh, Bondi. Sorry, Bondi.
Of course I was saying it wrong
-Was I yelling? -Bondi. No, not at all.
[ Laughter ]
-It's so hard. -You were not yelling, no.
Alright, come on. We can do it.
Here we go. -I don't even know what I said.
I think I spoke gibberish.
-This is so much harder than I thought.
[ Laughs ]
Fuggedaboutit.
Fuggedaboutit. -Thank about it.
-Fuggedaboutit.
Fuggedaboutit.
[ Laughter ]
Fuggedaboutit. -Think about it.
-Fuggedaboutit.
Fuggedaboutit!
[ Ding! ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
I once I got my head think about it...
-I helped you with the gesture.
-Oh, yeah, yeah, the gestures help.
Alright. I'll do gestures on this one.
-I totally probably made it worse.
-Yeah, here we go.
Are you ready? Or we good? -Oh, no.
-It's good?
[ Laughter ]
Labradoodle.
-The Lamassu.
-Labradoodle. Lamassu.
-Labradoodle.
-Labado...
-Sorry, okay.
-Labradoodle.
-It looks like Lamassu. I know you're not Lamassu that.
-Not Lamassu. This is Lamassu.
-Slap shoe. -No, no.
Ready?
No, that wasn't real.
L-Labradoodle.
[ Laughter ]
[ Applause ]
-One more.
-Labradoodle.
-Lama-- It looks like lamassu.
I don't know. [ Laughter ]
-It's not lamassu!
Labradoodle.
-Labrashu.
-Stop saying -- -Lama...
A Shih Tzu?
[ Laughter ]
No? -Labradoodle.
Doodle. Doodle.
-Lamassu.
[ Laughter ]
It looks like lamassu every time.
I know you're not saying it.
Labra -- Labradoodle.
-Lavashu. -Do.
-Shu. -Do.
-Do. -Shu.
[ Intimate music plays ]
-No, no.
[ Laughter ]
Labradoo-- Labra--
-Napping. -Labradoodle.
Napping dog. Napping.
Labradoodle.
Poodle.
-[ Grunting ]
-Sounds like a poodle?
-A Labradoodle?
Yes!
[ Ding! ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-Are you ready for this? -Yes. Yeah.
On your mark. Get set. Go!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
Don't get cocky.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-[ Squeals ] I'm spilling it.
Aah!
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Come on!
♪♪
[ Bell dinging ]
-Did you get it on your face?
-Completely. Ridiculous.
Margot Robbie, the champion!
The champion!
Alright, Margot. You go first.
Just look on the bottom of your coaster
and it should have a question on there.
I don't know what it is. -Okay.
The shot is called the Mary Queen of Shots.
-Ah. There you go. See, we're creative.
-That was clever. See what you did there.
Oh, no, I'm not gonna say...
[ Laughter ]
-You're having trouble saying the answer.
-No, I -- um,
the answer to that question --
I'm not proud of, but it would be --
also, I'm sorry to do this on Valentine's Day.
[ Audience murmurs, scattered laughter ]
-Also, I'm sorry to do this on Valentine's Day,
is your answer? -Yes.
-Also, I'm sorry to do this on Valentine's Day.
Did you -- You break up with someone?
You broke up with someone on Valentine's Day?
Oh, my gosh! [ Laughter ]
You really did that?
-It was awful. It was so bad.
-Why on Valentine's? Why didn't you wait, like, two days?
-I was planning to, and the conversation arose,
and I couldn't avoid it, and it happened, and it was awful.
It was really awful. -Oh, my gosh.
-I hope to God he's not watching this.
-Oh, my gosh. Sorry. I'm sorry, wow.
-Wait, so, do I have to do the shot or I don't have to do it?
-No, but you can do it if you feel it.
But you don't have to do it. You gave us the question.
-No, I'm good. -Alright.
[ Laughter ]
Here we go. My turn.
Alright, Mary Queen of Shots is the name of the shot.
Hmm. Hm.
Hmm...
♪♪
Howard Stern's house.
[ Laughter ]
-I so badly want to know this question.
-You're never going to.
[ Applause ]
Okay. -I feel like that could be
any number of things. How was it, by the way?
-It's actually spicy. -It looked spicy.
I thought -- -Something spicy in that thing.
-I was like, it looked like some sort of --
-That's exactly what it was. -That's adorable.
Oh. Okay.
Okay, this shot is called the Adíos Mofos.
[ Laughter ]
That's a great name. -That is a good name.
-Ooh, okay.
-Now you have reveal one of these -- oh, no.
You already revealed the question.
You don't have to, but I would.
[ Laughter ]
-No, no, no, that is not how --
I cannot reveal this question.
-Really? -No, I cannot.
No, absolutely not.
I can tell you the answer, though,
and the answer is Will Smith.
[ Audience oohs ]
But I cannot tell you the question, I'm afraid.
So I'm going to do the -- -Wait, wait, hold on.
Will Smith, though. Is this about "Suicide Squad"?
Is there gonna be another "Suicide Squad?"
-I've done two movies with Will. -Oh, interesting.
Yeah. I know, but, yeah, but I feel like those --
the "Suicide," those big superhero movies
you're not allowed to talk about.
-Make of it what you will, Jimmy, but I can't say.
-Does he die in the new "Suicide Squad"?!
Oh, my goodness.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Will Smith!
-That was nice. That was pretty nice.
-Will Smith. How was that?
-I think there was tequila in it.
Tequila and like blue food coloring, I guess.
-Adíos. -Adíos Mofos.
-Adíos, mofos.
Oh, gosh.
-You have to answer. Oh, no, we got three. Okay.
-Uh,
Michael Jordan.
I can say this one.
I will tell you this one.
Who is your worst kiss?
But let me explain. Let me explain.
[ Laughter ]
No, no, no. Let me tell you what happened.
-Please do. -Let me tell you what happened.
It wasn't that at all.
And it's Michael Jordan, not Michael B. Jordan.
-Not Michael B. Jordan.
-No, Michael Jordan the basketball player, legend.
-Either way, it's a good result.
-I was at a charity thing for Derek Jeter's golf tournament,
and I did this chip thing, at the end of the night,
they had some, like, thing -- like a dance thing afterwards,
at a dance club. -Where is this going, Jimmy?
-No, no, no, not at all. And he goes,
"Jimmy, do you know Michael?" And I go, "No.
I've never met him before," and I said hi to him.
And I went to give him, like, a kiss on the cheek here,
but he went to give me a kiss on the other cheek,
and we both, like, kissed each other.
It happened very fast, and I was, like, so scared,
and he just grabbed me and goes, "Don't worry about this."
[ Laughter ]
-In those big strong arms. He said, "You're safe."
[ Applause ] -Yeah. Don't --
don't worry about -- don't worry about that.
Don't worry about that.
It was very serious the way he said it to me.
-But it is very sweet, too, that when you meet another dude,
you go for a kiss on the cheek. I like that.
-You do? -Yeah, it's really sweet.
-Alright. Alright, here we go, pal.
Ready for this? We'll both read at the same time.
-Oh, okay.
-Because this last one here, it's the final round.
We're both going to answer the same question.
Okay. If we choose not to reveal what the question was,
we'll have to down this beer together.
-With straws, I see. -Yeah.
I'm wearing lipstick, so, yeah.
[ Laughter ]
Okay. Ready, pal? -Yeah, yeah.
-Here we go.
[ Laughter ]
Okay. Wait, maybe --
-These questions are asking for trouble.
-They really are. On the count of three.
Ready? One, two, three.
Kate Hudson. -I don't have one.
-Wait. What? -I don't have one.
-What do you mean? You don't have one?
-I have a rule and my rule --
-I have a rule, too.
-My rule prevents me from having an answer to that.
[ Laughs ]
-I just answered mine.
Well that's it -- -That's unfortunate for you.
-Yeah, I know, but we're drinking now, we're drinking.
-You said Kate Hudson?
-Yeah. -I want to know.
-Oh, my gosh. You didn't answer.
-I did answer. -Oh, you did answer. But you --
-So, you have to say the question
and you have to tell me. Please explain this.
[ Laughter ]
-Well, it's not even a big deal.
[ Sighs ]
Do you have a -- do you have a co-star
you thought you could have dated, but didn't?
[ Audience groans, laughter ]
I thought for a second -- I thought for a second
we hung out and we were friends,
and I -- This is a true story.
-Okay, okay, okay. -I thought maybe, you know,
maybe there could be something. She's cool, and we got along.
We were, like, super good friends.
After we did -- I took her to go see --
-How do you know each other? -No, we did a movie together.
-Okay, so first -- okay, okay, okay.
-No, we never, ever -- never did anything, no.
Never. -You were co-stars.
-Co-stars -- Well, "co-stars."
She was in the movie. I appeared in the movie.
[ Laughter ]
I never co-starred in a movie, let's be honest.
"Almost Famous." -Oh, my God.
You're in "Almost Famous"? -Yes!
[ Laughter, cymbal crashes ]
[ Applause ]
-I'm sorry.
-Did you blink?
Yeah, so I was in that movie, and we became friends.
And I had a beard.
I was the second manager that came in to take over the --
[ Laughter ]
Anyways, we're hanging out,
and I go -- one night we went to go see "Kids in the Hall."
We both like comedy, and I took her to see
"Kids in the Hall."
And we're at "Kids in the Hall," and she sees Chris Robinson,
the lead singer of the Black Crowes.
And we meet him for the first time.
And I go, "Hey, what's up? I'm a big fan."
Blah, blah, blah. And then the next day,
we we're going to go ice skating together in Central Park.
-Is that your idea of a date?
That's so sweet. I like that.
-So, we met and we went skating
and I put on my skates. And she called me before
and she goes, "Hey, do you have any Black Crowes CDs?"
And I go, "Yeah, of course."
She goes, "Can you bring them over?"
So I go, "Sure, yeah. I'll bring them by the ice rink."
So, I brought them to ice skating.
-Nothing clicked? -No,
I thought she was just friends and she wanted to borrow them
since she was in town. -Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
-So, I go over and I go -- we ice skated
maybe three or four times around the rink and then I go,
"So, what are you doing now?"
She goes, "I've got to go because I have a date with
Chris Robinson from the Black Crowes."
[ Sad tuba plays ]
The lead singer of the Black Crowes.
I go, "Well, yeah. That's of course what you're doing."
I'm, like, on skates. I'm taking my skates off.
-Tears running down your face. -Crying on the inside.
I go like this -- You clearly had no -- But --
-You thought it was a date and she didn't know it was a date.
-She ended up marrying Chris Robinson
and having a baby.
They had a baby and everything.
She had no intention or anything --
-And they named it Jimmy, so it's okay.
-And I never got my CDs back!
Oh, gosh. I'm so embarrassed.
Margot, why don't you pick the first box?
-I go first? -Yeah, please.
You good at this? -Mmm.
-You good at lying? -I'm a terrible liar, actually.
Or is that a lie, and I'm really good at this?
-Ooh!
That was sneaky already. -I'm in your head, Jimmy.
I'm in your head. -I know, yeah.
Oh, oh, I can see the box is a bit heavy.
-It is.
-Yeah. Oh, maybe not.
Okay, good. Alright.
-Hey, hey. [ Suspenseful music plays ]
Ooh! -Hey, hey, ooh?
-Saucy! -Saucy?
[ Laughter ]
-It's kind of risqué for... -Really?
-I mean, it is a late-night show.
Sure, but, like... -Risqué?
[ Laughter ]
-Ooh! Oh! -Really?
Saucy? Something saucy on my show?
Risqué? -I mean, it's kind of sexy.
Like, I...
[ Laughter ]
I mean...
You're kind of in it.
-Okay? -Um...
-Wow. -...'cause it's your head,
and it's, like, the body of, like, the char--
like, Jess-- the red-dress lady,
Jessica Rabbit. Roger Rabbit?
Jessica Rabbit? -Yeah, from "Roger Rabbit"?
-Yeah, it's your head... -My head on...
-...and her body. And you look great.
-...Jessica Rabbit's body. -You look good.
-And I look good. -You look great.
[ Laughter ]
-My head...
has never been in doll form.
[ Laughter ]
-I mean... -Really?
So it's my head? Maybe someone made my head
and put on a Jessica Rabbit body?
-It's a bobble-head sort of -- Like a bobble-head doll.
-I did have a bobble-head done. -Oh, you did?
-Yeah. -Right, well, here it is.
[ Laughter ]
-Yeah, but the bobble-head's a giant head.
It would have to be a giant Jessica Rabbit.
I don't know if that's just physically...
-It looks good. I think it looks good.
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. [ Laughs ]
See, right there, you just... -They should sell this.
-...you just busted yourself.
I think...you lie!
-[ Laughing ] I did.
-You did?
[ Bell dings ] Oh, is that a lobster?
[ Cheers and applause ]
Oh, that was actually pretty good!
-[ Laughs ] -That was very good!
I was like, "Wait. It's not much to do with that lobster."
-Okay, here we go. -It was like a red theme.
-No, you're very good. What am I looking for?
[ Audience shouting ]
No problem. Here we go. -Do I put the box down?
-Oh, sure. -Okay.
[ Light laughter ]
-[ Grunting ]
-Oh, come on. -[ Grunting ]
-Please. -[ Grunting ]
-I'm not falling for this trick. -Oh!
Oh, my back! -[ Laughs ]
-My back is killing me, oh.
Oh, saucy! [ Suspenseful music plays ]
-Saucy?
-Yeah.
Saucy.
[ Laughter ]
-That sexy, huh?
-I don't know what to make of this.
-I'm very familiar with this.
-Okay. -It's -- It's ice cream...
-Oh. -...in a --
Looks like a Houston Astros hat, like, baseball hat,
upside-down baseball hat.
But interesting enough, they have a Trump hair --
It looks like Trump hair is sprinkled on top.
[ Laughter ]
-Just wanna recap. Um... -Yeah, no problem.
-There's ice cream? -Ice cream in a plastic,
upside-down baseball cap.
-I'm gonna say that's a lie.
-Gosh, you're so right. -Yes!
[ Bell dings ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
I didn't know what to do. I don't even know --
That's so bizarre, I didn't know how to make anything up right.
-That is really bizarre. -This is the --
This is the tie-breaker right here.
Whoever wins the next round wins the whole thing.
-I hate losing to you, Jimmy. I don't want to lose.
-No, hey, I won't let you lose unless you do.
[ Laughter ]
Margot, alright, you choose -- You choose the box in this one.
Audience, which...
[ Audience shouting ]
-That's my favorite number, so I'm gonna go with it.
-Alright, yeah. Do you like two?
-Yeah. -Is that your birthday?
-Yeah, I'm born on the 2nd. How original.
-Hey, no, I like that.
-Ooh! Actually, kind of heavy.
-Alright. That kind of sounded heavy, too.
So, here we go. [ Suspenseful music plays ]
Oh, thank you, Roots.
Now they're playing music. Now I can't hear anything.
-[ Laughs ] -Alright.
This is all part of the thing.
Alright. I'm looking at your reaction.
-Oh.
[ Laughter ]
It's a, uh...
-Would I have this on my desk at work?
-Most probably.
[ Laughter ]
I think most people would have it, like, on their desk.
[ Cheers ]
-Don't play! Don't play along, please.
[ Laughter ]
-Be on my side. -Alright.
What is it, what is it? -It's kind of like a --
This is why it could be on your desk.
You could use it as a paperweight.
-Okay.
-But you probably wouldn't, but you could if you wanted to.
It's kind of like a dish, like a salad-y,
glass crystal-y ball. -Uh-huh.
-Um, and...
It's filled with Band-Aids, so that's kind of gross.
So you wouldn't have that on your desk.
-No, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, open Band-Aids?
-No, they're just, like, the Band-Aid packets.
-Okay. -And then, there's, like,
a little toy car just sitting on the top.
I don't know what it's doing.
Yeah. -You kind of lost
your accent a little bit describing it.
[ Laughter ]
So, that makes me think that -- You'd be like,
[Cockney accent] "There's a Band-Aid in a bowl -- in a bowl,
a paperweight."
-[Cockney accent] A paperweight.
-[Normal voice] You didn't say...
You said, "It's a Band-Aid in a, uh,
A-O-O-A-O-A-O!"
-"Hey, hey, it's kinda like a Band-Aid."
-Oh, I'm gonna say you lie!
-Yes, I lied. -Yes!
Oh, my God! [ Bell dinging ]
What was it? [ Cheers and applause ]
Oh, it's Nicholas Cage on an egg in a bird...